♪♪♪
♪ NICE TO MEET YOU ♪
♪ WHERE YOU BEEN? ♪
♪ I COULD SHOW YOU
INCREDIBLE THINGS ♪
♪ MAGIC, MADNESS, HEAVEN, SIN ♪
♪ SAW YOU THERE AND I THOUGHT ♪
♪ OH MY GOD ♪
♪ LOOK AT THAT FACE ♪
♪ YOU LOOK LIKE
MY NEXT MISTAKE ♪
♪ LOVE'S A GAME,
WANT TO PLAY? ♪
♪ NEW MONEY,
SUIT AND TIE ♪
♪ I CAN READ YOU LIKE
A MAGAZINE ♪
♪ AIN'T IT FUNNY,
RUMORS FLY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW YOU HEARD
ABOUT ME ♪
♪ SO HEY, LET'S
BE FRIENDS ♪
♪ I'M DYING TO SEE HOW
THIS ONE ENDS ♪
♪ GRAB YOUR PASSPORT,
AND MY HAND ♪
♪ I CAN MAKE THE BAD
GUYS GOOD ♪
♪ FOR A WEEKEND ♪
♪ SO IT'S GONNA
BE FOREVER ♪
♪ OR IT'S GONNA GO
DOWN IN FLAMES ♪
♪ YOU CAN TELL ME
WHEN IT'S OVER ♪
♪ IF THE HIGH WAS
WORTH THE PAIN ♪
♪ GOT A LONG LIST
OF EX LOVERS ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU
I'M INSANE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU KNOW I
LOVE THE PLAYERS ♪
♪ AND YOU LOVE
THE GAME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE YOUNG
AND WE'RE ♪
♪ RECKLESS, WE'LL TAKE
THIS WAY TOO FAR ♪
♪ IT'LL LEAVE
YOU BREATHLESS ♪
♪ OR WITH A NASTY SCAR ♪
♪ GOT A LONG LIST OF
EX LOVERS ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU
I'M INSANE ♪
♪ BUT I'VE GOT A
BLANK SPACE, ♪
♪ BABY... ♪
♪ AND I'LL WRITE
YOUR NAME. ♪
♪♪♪
♪ CHERRY LIPS,
CRYSTAL SKIES ♪
♪ I COULD SHOW YOU
INCREDIBLE THINGS ♪
♪ STOLEN KISSES,
PRETTY LIES ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE KING,
BABY, I'M YOUR ♪
♪ QUEEN FIND OUT
WHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ BE THAT GIRL FOR
A MONTH ♪
♪ WAIT, THE WORST IS
YET TO ♪
♪ COME... ♪
♪ SCREAMING,
CRYING, PERFECT ♪
♪ STORMS ♪
♪ I CAN MAKE ALL THE
TABLES TURN ♪
♪ ROSE GARDEN FILLED
WITH THORNS ♪
♪ KEEP YOU SECOND
GUESSING LIKE ♪
♪ OH MY GOD ♪
♪ WHO IS SHE? ♪
♪ I GET DRUNK
ON JEALOUSY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'LL COME BACK ♪
♪ EACH TIME YOU LEAVE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE DARLING, I'M
A NIGHTMARE ♪
♪ DRESSED LIKE
A DAYDREAM ♪
♪ SO IT'S GONNA
BE FOREVER ♪
♪ OR IT'S GONNA GO
DOWN IN FLAMES ♪
♪ YOU CAN TELL ME WHEN
IT'S OVER ♪
♪ IF THE HIGH WAS
WORTH THE PAIN ♪
♪ GOT A LONG LIST OF
EX LOVERS ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU
I'M INSANE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU KNOW I
LOVE THE PLAYERS ♪
♪ AND YOU LOVE
THE GAME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE YOUNG
AND WE'RE ♪
♪ RECKLESS, WE'LL TAKE
THIS WAY TOO FAR ♪
♪ IT'LL LEAVE
YOU BREATHLESS ♪
♪ OR WITH A NASTY SCAR ♪
♪ GOT A LONG LIST OF
EX LOVERS ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU
I'M INSANE ♪
♪ BUT I'VE GOT A
BLANK SPACE, ♪
♪ BABY... ♪
♪ AND I'LL WRITE
YOUR NAME. ♪
♪ BOYS ONLY WANT LOVE
IF IT'S TORTURE ♪
♪ DON'T SAY I DIDN'T,
SAY I DIDN'T WARN ♪
♪ YOU... ♪
♪ BOYS ONLY WANT LOVE
IF IT'S TORTURE ♪
♪ DON'T SAY I DIDN'T,
SAY I DIDN'T WARN ♪
♪ YOU... ♪
♪ SO IT'S GONNA
BE FOREVER ♪
♪ OR IT'S GONNA GO
DOWN IN FLAMES ♪
♪ YOU CAN TELL ME WHEN
IT'S OVER ♪
♪ IF THE HIGH WAS
WORTH THE PAIN ♪
♪ GOT A LONG LIST OF
EX LOVERS ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU
I'M INSANE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU KNOW I
LOVE THE PLAYERS ♪
♪ AND YOU LOVE
THE GAME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE YOUNG
AND WE'RE ♪
♪ RECKLESS, WE'LL TAKE
THIS WAY TOO FAR ♪
♪ IT'LL LEAVE
YOU BREATHLESS ♪
♪ OR WITH A NASTY SCAR ♪
♪ GOT A LONG LIST OF
EX LOVERS ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU
I'M INSANE ♪
♪ BUT I'VE GOT A
BLANK SPACE, ♪
♪ BABY... ♪
♪ AND I'LL
WRITE YOUR NAME. ♪
♪♪♪